JoJo...
I've heard so much about you.
Listen, and listen good.
San Viento here, the so-called Pillar Man,
uses a mask to turn men into vampires.
He does this to make them
stronger, and then he devours them.
Destroy him!
Take him out while there's still time!
Don't do it, Jojo!
He's dangerous!
You're it!
Oh, I get it.
You're one of those strong
silent types, right?
Ever thought about modeling?
You've got a nice look there.
Come on, let's see what you've got.
Give me a smile.
I know you can do it.
Show me some vulnerability.
Work with me here.
Make some love to the camera.
Ready? Sit! Give me happy!
Now be silly!
Show us those pearly whites!
Come on, big guy.
Smile at the birdie. Jojo!
Stop this nonsense immediately!
Don't provoke him!
Please, Jojo, send me
into his dangerous! Yeah.
I know you think he's dangerous, but I
have a theory that maybe he's not so bad.
Let me test something out here.
I don't want to assume he's evil just
because he killed a bunch of brainless...
What are you, insane?
If he's not evil, why did he
kill all my men? Don't know.
Some would say you're
responsible for what's happened.
Weren't you the one
experimenting on him and
trying to blast him
away in the first place?
Not that I really care about that.
The only reason I'm here
is to make sure that
Speedwagon makes it back
to New York safe and south.
Anyway, I'm not here to fight.
And I'm feeling generous.
Come on, loosen up, big guy.
How about that smile?
That was rude.
He just walked through me
like I wasn't even there.
Who the hell does this guy think he is?
Maybe I should teach him a quick lesson.
Have a nice trip.
What the
hell was that?
That was the weirdest feeling and it hurt.
What is this?
This tool, cold and long,
with many different pieces.
He does understand!
He's not simply mimicking!
It took him practically no time at
all to completely master our language!
How...
how is he doing that?
He took it apart.
He dismantled that entire weapon
like some expert gunsmith.
It takes a soldier dozens of hours to learn
how to fieldstrip his weapon that fast.
He's using his advanced
intellect to learn everything.
So bright.
This light is new to me.
What is it? Don't you see?
We weren't the ones
observing all this time.
He was actually watching us.
Hey, big guy.
You want to learn a new joke?
Just stop me if you've
heard this one before.
Knock, knock.
Jojo, get away!
You are playing games, Primitive.
I do not want to play games.
What the?
Ribblades, sometimes
known as fighting ribs.
They're capable of being
manipulated in any direction. Jojo!
Sparks energy.
This human seems
different from the others.
I was not able to absorb
his body into mine.
He just flew away.
And somehow, his leg, it remains.
It still seems fine.
This one is something new.
I have yet to see such a human.
Is he a unique specimen?
Or do all humans of his particular
class possess the same properties?
Could it be related to age?
Ah, now I see.
My instinct was right.
That human is unique.
Jojo, please!
Make it stop, please!
Speed wagon!
That bastard!
Let the old man go, San Viento!
Now I'm in the mood!
Come on, big guy, you
wanna try and take me on?
It would seem that humans
have evolved their confidence.
Hope you're hungry!
One Hamon sandwich coming up!
Huh?
What the devil?
My Harmon is making that blood float.
Something's wrong here.
My Harmon is running off him
like rain off a raincoat.
He's somehow repelling it and
pushing it into all of this blood.
I don't understand it.
His skin is acting like a ground.
Somehow it's behaving
just like Straitzo's scar.
My body and his body seem to be
repelling against one another.
Whoa!
What?
What have you done to my hand?
Wait.
It's still there.
But check it out.
I can completely remove my thumb.
Doesn't anyone have a sense of humor left?
Come on, guys.
This is funny stuff here.
But seriously, folks.
Lucky thing I rolled
my wrist just in time.
The beast's immune to Hamon.
That's not true, Jojo!
Don't you see?
It was Hamon that was protecting you!
It kept your body from being
completely absorbed into that thing!
Idiot!
It's like eating a blowfish for him!
He knows he must kill it first
and then remove the poison part!
That is how San Viento plans
on absorbing Jojo's body!
Well, too bad for him I'm not a blowfish.
Regardless, I need to think
of something fast here.
Maybe it's time to make
my emergency escape.
You can't do that!
The danger of San Viento
escaping is too high!
No one leaves until he's dead!
Oh, shut up!
You released this monster,
and now you're saying you need
someone else to clean up the mess?
I don't need anything else
on my plate, Von Stroheim!
Let's see if I can inject some hormone
into his system with something sharp!
His skin is malleable like rubber.
See if you can dodge this one, big guy!
How about a dose of
hormone right in the eye?
I hope you're ready for
your can't-miss close-up!
What?
That's impossible!
Even his eyes feel like
they're some kind of rubber!
Jojo, get out of there right now!
Jojo!
That hit to the solar plexus
completely knocked the wind out of him!
He seems to create his own energy.
He controls it with his breathing.
But lying there now, unconscious, he
is as vulnerable as any other human.
Jojo!
You've got to use your harm on breathing!
You've got to breathe!
Use your harm on breathing!
Breathe, damn it!
Breathe!
No!
There's no stopping him!
I've got to initiate a
self-destruct sequence!
For the Fatherland!
I wouldn't do that if I were you!
Everyone just calm down here.
Looks like my gamble paid off.
Figuring that attacks
from outside are no good,
I'm going to send some Hamon into
him while he tries to enjoy his meal!
Jojo!
I waited for you to start devouring me.
This is gonna be fun!
Enjoy your Hamon Blast!
I...
I think I get it.
Now that I've seen him from
the inside, I understand.
His whole body is one
big digestive system.
Every one of his cells, they're all
filled with aggressive digestive enzymes,
making it possible to dissolve his prey.
It looks like he's absorbing them, when
actually he's digesting them whole.
Harmon, that was what kept
me from being digested.
I sent it inside him
when he tried to eat me.
Jojo, your Harmon wasn't enough.
You have to find a way to
completely destroy San Viento.
The separated parts of San Viento
are trying to connect to one another.
That's pretty much exactly
what happened with Streetser.
Lucky me, I figured you would
try to go and do the same thing.
Von Stroheim!
Come on, get a hold of yourself!
Does this thing have any weaknesses?
Uh, sunlight, yeah! That's it!
It was there, on the walls of the cave.
Sunlight is his natural enemy.
The very reason he made the masks in
the first place was to conquer the sun!
Are you insane?
What are you doing?
You can't let San Viento
escape into the outside world!
On the contrary, I think he needs
to go on a nice sunlit stroll.
He's running out of breath.
He won't be able to control his harmone.
He hasn't had enough training with it.
This fight has completely exhausted him.
Cease this foolishness
now, you lowly primitive.
Remember!
You must control your hormone breathing!
If I could breathe, I probably wouldn't
be so tired in the first place!
Come on, big guy!
I think we've all had
just about enough of you!
But fortunately for me,
we're just a few steps away from the
two of us catching some nice rays!
What the hell?
I can't move!
I feel so heavy!
What?
What's happening to me?
Meat invade, also known as foul flesh.
They're pieces of his flesh!
They're...
they're feeding on me!
You...
you son of a...
Got to stay focused!
I never once imagined a human such as
you would be born during my slumber.
What?
Joestar, leave the rest to me,
Colonel Rudolf von Stroheim.
Opening the door will end all this.
Allow me to help you
destroy this vile creature.
Wow, von Stroheim.
I would have never thought.
Hm, well-attempted, primitives.
I can almost reach the door!
A meaningless struggle.
This is bad.
Joestar, get up!
Don't just lie there like a baby.
I'm trying to think here.
If you hadn't noticed,
we're both in deep trouble.
Silence!
Do you see those axes
on the wall next to you?
Reach up and grab one.
Take one and chop off my leg.
I can't do that.
You coward, cut off my leg.
It's the only way we're
getting that door open.
Maybe you're right, but
are you sure about this?
I mean, there has got
to be some other way.
Do as I say.
He's recovering, Joestar.
But I'm no doctor!
I have no idea how to do this right!
I am a proud servant of the Wehrmacht!
I am prepared to do whatever
is required to fulfill my duty!
I proudly give up my
leg for the Fatherland!
Now hurry up before it's too late!
Damn it!
Do it now, Joestar!
Okay, I'll do it!
If you really want me to chop
it off, then off it goes!
I demand that you chop it off now!
Ow!
I figured this guy was just some bloated
power monger, but I gotta hand it to him.
He's got guts.
I wish there was some other way, but if
he's courageous enough, then forgive me!
Aaaaah!
Tell me big guy, how does that
sunshine feel on your skin?
Aaaaah!
He did it!
What's he doing?
Aaaaaah!
Help me!
That monster's trying
to crawl inside my leg!
Get out of there, you!
Whoa, this is a shock.
Von Stroheim's basically okay,
and he's free of any harm.
Damn it!
You get out of me! Run, Viento!
I can't believe this thing's willpower.
I've never seen anything like it.
If he stays inside von Stroheim, he'll be
totally fine even here in broad daylight!
I can feel him!
This can't be real!
Do you want to know what the
worst part about this is?
My leg doesn't even hurt anymore!
It feels pleasant, you believe that?
Oh my god!
Von Stroheim!
Wait, what are you doing?
Put it down, Von Stroheim! Stay back!
You've seen what horrible
things San Viento is capable of!
There is no hope!
My destiny has been determined!
So now, all I can do is
destroy the both of us!
But I have one more thing to say
to you before my time is done!
If you know what's good for you,
you'll listen close, Englishman.
We did not awaken San Viento simply for
scientific research or military gain.
Then why?
Why did you risk it? Tell me!
Silence!
It's your destiny to hear these
words from my lips, Joe Starr.
San Viento is just the tip of the iceberg.
The Wehrmacht has discovered
another pillar in Europe.
We now know that San Viento is not
the only one of his kind around.
Wait so there's more of them
where are they tell me Von
Stroheim where I'm sorry but I
don't have that answer for you
Joestar there are more pillar
men out there and they have
powers that are beyond our
wildest imagination for millennia
those powers have remained
dormant but that won't last and
soon they will awaken you must
find another weakness other
than just sunlight or else
hope is lost that's why we were
experimenting on San Viento we
were looking for that weakness.
There's a battle against the
Pillar Man yet to be fought.
The events of 50 years ago
call upon you for that battle.
Listen to me.
You will need more than just
your Hamon to overcome them.
You must go to Rome.
There you will find
someone who can help you.
It is someone that your
speed wagon knows very well.
San Viento is trying to move my party
into that well so he can hide again.
But he can't stop me from opening up my
body completely to let the sun shine in!
Von Stroheim, don't you dare.
Human greatness lies in having the
courage to face down one's fears.
Do you know who said that?
The Greek historian Plutarch.
Farewell.
You annoying Englishman!
Don't do it!
I still have questions for you!
Monster!
Damn that crazy German and all his honor!
I'm sure that we could
have found another way!
Cezriato!
You annoy me!
Primitive, I will destroy you!
Steady your breathing.
Use your hormone technique.
Primitive, why oppose me?
You were doomed here from the start!
Ha!
I know just what you're going to say next!
You'll say I've seen right through
you all this time, Joestar!
I've seen right through
It's high noon over this well!
The sun reflecting off of the
water should cook you nicely!
Although I doubt you even thought of that!
You were thinking about jumping under the
night's cool water and
getting out of the sun,
right?
Well, screw that idea!
I'm not letting you touch the water!
I'm alive, thanks to the sun.
He's a statue now.
But!
We finally got that smile.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you.
Out and out!
I spend the day your way.
Call it morning.
Driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I'll spend the day your way.
Cold and mooding, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
When my lover will be there.
And we'll see you?
My grandfather died tragically.
You couldn't even beat
one of those pigeons.
Quickly, bring out more UV lamps.
Now is the time.
Awaken, my masters.
Amen.